Hello, Kawajiri residence.
JULY 16TH (FRI) 7:57 AM
Huh? I'm sorry,
you have the wrong number.
Really… Superb job, Hayato.
So you've kept that irksome
Rohan at bay.
I said you've got the wrong number.
Goodbye.
- Misdialed call.
- Now, then…
I have to provide for
my sweet, beautiful family.
But first,
I wonder if a certain someone
will allow me to give her
a goodbye kiss?
Huh?
What are you doing?!
My expensive china…
Why would you do such a thing?!
I never know what's going on
inside that head of yours!
You act like you don't
even hear me! Why?!
I just…
Mom, he's no ordinary person.
If I so much as utter a word
about him to anyone,
the listener will be
blown to smithereens,
and time will reset to morning.
If we keep letting him
have free reign overall our lives,
maybe not now, but eventually,
we will die by his hands.
R-Rohan Kishibe…
But there is someone else
who has special powers like Kira.
I've got to talk to
Rohan Kishibe somehow.
The only one who can save us
and beat Kira
is someone with special powers
like Rohan Kishibe!
He's here. It's Rohan.
If I approach Rohan directly,
he'll be killed by explosives…
Then I'll be forced to
relive that same morning.
I've got to figure out a way
to tell Rohan the info
without meeting him face to face.
It's time to alter destiny's plans!
FLIP
W-What's going on?!
[WARNING]
DO NOT READ ON.
It's what Rohan did to me
that morning from before!
Dammit.
But I was hidden
from Rohan this time!
Rohan didn't even see me!
Once the wheels of fate
are set in motion,
there's no turning back…
Hayato.
Breakdown, Breakdown
(Listen up)
Let the voice of love
take you higher
Let the gathering forces
overcome time itself
Let the joy of love
give you an answer
Our Willis unbreakable
even when it's time to part
1999 Bizarre Summer
This is the hymn born from
our fearless hearts
Great Days
Breakdown, Breakdown
JOJO'S BIZARRE ADVENTURE
DIAMOND IS UNBREAKABLE
July 16th (Fri) 8:27 AM
Ugh, the weather report
never said anything about rain.
EPISODE 36
BITES THE DUST, PART 2
You may think you broke that
teapot out of your own free will,
but you'd be wrong.
It's simply a re-occurrence
of the pot breaking
from the previous morning.
It's preordained.
That is how fate works.
If Rohan transformed your noggin
into a book the morning before,
then it is a book you shall be.
That, my boy, is what makes Deadly
Queen's Bites the Dust unstoppable.
It makes the exposure
of my identity
as if it never happened,
reversing time in the process.
Which means I get to enjoy watching
Rohan explode into obsolescence
before I jaunt off to work.
IT RAINED.
AT 8:27 AM, LIGHTNING STRUCK
ABOVE THE PEPSI SIGN.
I can't let Rohan die!
I have to save Rohan!
Ah, Rohan Kishibe.
Now watch.
He has no idea why
he's about to breathe his last.
"My life as a manga artist is over…"
Must be tearing through
his head right now.
R-Rohan…
No, god, please!
Hayato, your visit with Rohan
is now as if it never happened,
and the morning will go on
as it always would.
Of course,
if I undo Bites the Dust now,
Rohan's death will become
not temporary but ever lasting…
But for now,
I'll let it do its thing.
I expect a few of his friends
to come join the party.
You will exterminate them
automatically for me.
You're my own personal landmine.
But Bites the Dust will leave you
completely unharmed,
so relax, do whatever
you school boys do.
Well, time for Dad
to head to the station.
No slacking at school now.
It's my fault.
He crossed paths with me…
He crossed paths with me
and was murdered!
Isn't there something I can do
to defeat this monster?
Um… Pardon me,
but I have a question…
You wouldn't happen to
have the time, would you?
My watch seems to be out of whack.
Hello? Anyone home?
It's 8:33…
Huh? I have this weird feeling
I've seen you somewhere before…
Where was it?
Do you know who I am?
No…
Oh, I guess it's all in my head.
Sorry for
the off-the-wall question.
8:33… Thanks!
Mr. Jotaro! So it is after 8:30.
Strange, I wonder where
Rohan-sensei went.
Rohan Kishibe's friends!
They planned to meet here!
- He left the car door
- They must have
- wide open
- the same kind of powers…
- and the key in the ignition.
- They're here to question me
- Rohan-sensei would never do that…
- about Yoshikage Kira.
No! If they figure out
I'm Hayato Kawajiri and start
- interrogating me about Dad…
- That's Rohan-Sensei's earring.
Oops, sorry…
I overslept and am supposed to
meet up with my friends.
Hey… I've seen that face before…
Now where?
Ah, Josuke and Okuyasu.
Yo.
Yo, Koichi.
Top of the morning to ya, Jotaro.
- A-And two more…
- What, so the only one
- He said more of them
- we're waiting for is Rohan?
Would be showing up…
- He was talking about them!
- How the hell are we supposed to
find Hayato Kawajiri
without him here.
Sorry, I forgot I was still
hanging on to this.
Here. Your hat.
Th-Thanks…
When I look at his face
from this angle…
That angle. I know I've seen
that face somewhere…
But where?
Where have I seen that face…
Koichi. Look at the name
on his backpack.
Huh?
HAYATO KAWAJIRI
Hayato Kawajiri?!
What?!
They figured me out!
WAKE UP
WEATHER REPORT BEGINS
KIRA LEAVES HOUSE
HAYATO MEETS ROHAN
LIGHTNING STRIKES PEPSI SIGN
EXPLOSION KILLS ROHAN KISHIBE
JULY 16TH (FRI) 8:34 AM
Hayato Kawajiri…
What are you doing here?
Was all this planned?
Could this have something
to do with Rohan-sensei?
If they start questioning me
about Dad…
There's no question… the bomb
will kill every one of them!
N-No!
Don't ask me any questions…
If you guys get killed,
then who's gonna kill him?
If I have to dupe them,
then so be it…
Whatever it takes…
I can't let them die!
I have something I'd like to
ask you about this photo…
I'd like to know the reason
behind your video recording.
Why were you taking video of you—
Nosebleed!
I have to go to the doctor!
I-I don't know why
there's so much blood!
Sorry… Gotta go!
Hold it.
You said you got a nosebleed,
let's see.
Here. What happened?
I have to go. I'm sorry.
You don't have to see a doctor.
Your nose isn't bleeding.
Huh?
Huh?!
I'm Josuke Higashikata.
And I'm related to that guy,
Jotaro Kujo.
The guy with the dumb-ass grin
is Okuyasu Nijimura.
And the face that shouts
world's nicest guy
belongs to Koichi Hirose.
You go to
Budogaoka Elementary, right?
You still got some time
before classes start.
We won't take much of your time…
Now about this picture.
If it's nothing,
we'll just be on our way.
It is something!
Just don't ask me any questions!
You can't ask me any questions!
Is the person in this picture
your da—
No! Don't say any more!
So I guess that's it…
Now they're going to ask
even more questions.
What do you mean
"Don't say anymore"?
They're all doing it now…
What shouldn't we say?
There's nothing I can do now!
Is this about your dad?
The bomb's gonna get them!
It's gonna get them all!
You blurted out, "No!"
"Don't say any more"?
But we never even
asked you anything.
I have a feeling…
- The bomb's gonna get them…
- the mere act of questioning him
- The bomb… The bomb…
- Is what's sending him into a panic.
That's it…
I-If I die,
they'll still be able to live!
I'm the bomb, I have to die!
With me out of the picture,
I know they'll defeat that devil
and save Mom!
Come on, let's just ask him
about Kosaku Kawajiri already.
Wait, Josuke. Something's up.
What's going on, what's wrong?
I can't do it…
Something's keeping me
from slashing my throat!
That's…
That Stand…
I've never forgotten that face!
Deadly Queen!
Actually,
you're looking at Deadly Queen's
bomb type three, Bites the Dust.
To attack now would be futile.
You see me now because I
have already entered your pupils.
The number of you
is inconsequential,
for in a single instant…
Your folly was searching
for my true identity!
What, you're already awake?
I'm glad you finally
decided to answer me,
but there's no need
to scream at me.
Breakfast is ready,
come and get it.
I couldn't stop him…
He got them too.
It's all over now…
No matter what I do,
in one hour, fate will wipe them
off the face of the earth…
I can't even kill myself.
My death would hinder his plan,
so Bites the Dust is programmed
to protect me.
He's unstoppable…
Yoshikage Kira is
a horrible, horrible monster.
Unless he dies
or decides to shut off Bites
the Dust at exactly the right time,
those guys are gonna die for sure.
Unless he dies or shuts off Bites
the Dust at exactly the right time…
I never thought I could ever
be capable of killing a person.
How could a puny 11-year-old kid
ever kill a monster like him…
There is one way!
An 11-year-old little punk
can kill him…
…with one thing.
I've got my own secret weapon
slumbering in the shadows
of the attic.
For the first time in my life,
I found myself begging
and praying to God.
Dear God, help me find
the strength to kill this man.
So I was right.
The sun makes this cat plant
spring to life,
then it attacks by shooting
bullets of com pressed air.
The power it can generate with
such little light is incredible.
This killer instinct…
I'll use its killer instinct,
and send an air bullet
flying his way point blank.
Pointblank…
But when and how?
I can't do it inside or nearby.
Mom's here.
That's it… My hat!
He'll put that hat on my head.
That'll be my chance!
He'll come up right behind me,
right in point-blank range.
That's when I'll get him!
What? You're kidding!
We're already on air?
Er, um… It's now 7:55…
Dad said he wanted
another cup of coffee.
Hello?
Nope, wrong number.
This isn't the Sakurai residence.
Sweetie, I have something special
here for you.
A pipping hot cup of fresh coffee.
Oh, that's right…
What a pleasant morning.
I suppose one more cup
before work wouldn't hurt.
Everything is set in stone under
Bites the Dust's power, right?
Once something is broken,
it's destined to break again,
and there's not a damn thing
I can do.
You said it yourself
My favorite china tea set!
Take that ass!
All right, Mom, I'm off to school!
I'm looking out for you.
I'll never let anyone
hurt you, Mom!
I'm in disbelief.
I never have any idea what's
going on in that boy's head… But…
Then there are days
he reminds me how much I love him.
Oh, please don't. I can clean up.
There's no use crying
over spilled milk.
The important thing is that
you're okay, did it burn you?
No… I'm perfectly fine.
Still not here…
H-He's not here…
He's nowhere to be seen.
S-Something's off.
Last time, he was already here
by this time…
Why isn't he here?
Darn, the weather report
never said anything about rain!
I-It's starting to rain!
Did I change destiny
by leaving the house before him?
No, that's impossible!
As long as he tries to
put the hat on my head,
there's no question
he'd approach me from behind.
L-Lightning struck the Pepsi sign!
Calm down. Relax!
I've still got two minutes!
I have more than two minutes
before Rohan Kishibe
spontaneously explodes.
I just have to believe—
In the shadows of the tree…
He's already here!
Under any other circumstance,
I'd say this is a pleasant morning.
But Hayato wasn't himself…
What's going on?
It's just a feeling,
a strange feeling…
We've relived this morning
several times now…
Probably three,
no four times at least.
Does he sense something's up?
It doesn't matter,
there's no time!
I'll just have to blast him
from here.
Could he know
I'm holding the cat plant…
Is that why
he's staying back there?
No… If he knew,
he wouldn't be that close.
I'll have to knock him off
with one shot.
If I miss, Rohan will explode,
his friends will be obliterated,
and that murderer'll deactivate
Bites the Dust.
If that happens,
he ends up the victor!
There's no more time! Shit…
Just one more step to the left!
Just step out from the shadow
of that shitty tree
so I can blow you away
to kingdom come!
What?! H-He just hid himself
even more!
The look in Hayato's eyes
this morning at the house…
He radiated a certain tenacity
I've never seen before.
The same look
that annoying Koichi Hirose
and vile Josuke give off
Something tells me
I need to watch his every move…
Then again,
Hayato is completely helpless…
Shit, I'm screwed!
A few seconds past 8:29,
and the bomb will start
ripping apart Rohan Kishibe!
The brat is panic-stricken…
like a desperate rat,
toiling and drowning
in a cesspool of filth.
I guess his tenacity was
just a figment of my imagination.
Those are the eyes of
complete and utter defeat.
So he finally came out!
I came here to bring you
your hat, Hayato.
If you're listening up there,
thank you, God.
Thank you for
making that murderer
leave the safety
of that tree's shadow!
I'm ready to do this!
Suck on this, Yoshikage Kira!
What?!
I did it!
A clean shot! I… I did it!
Hayato Kawajiri's
nowhere to be seen…
Perhaps he took
a different route to school.
Prepare to die, murderer!
W-W-What?!
Lately…
Impossible!
My nails have exhibited
unprecedented growth…
Which got me thinking
how lately my life
has been devoid
of all that is good.
But the contents of this pocket…
confirm my feeling
that a guardian angel
has returned to watch over me
from last night.
Remember when I broke
Mom's special tea cup?
The coffee spilled on my wrist,
giving me a nasty burn,
so I took off the watch
and placed it safe and sound
in my chest pocket.
And Io and behold!
Had I not spilled that coffee…
How… Howie that possible? I…
I… I blew it!
That horrible moment
is almost here!
EPISODE 37
SHINING D (DIAMOND)
IS UNBREAKABLE, PART 1